export default data = [
  {
      question: "I called the airline to ______ my flight reservation a week before I left for Canada.",
      options: ["expand","attach","confirm","strengthen"],
      correct_option: "confirm"
  },
  {
      question: "In order to write a report on stars, we decided to ______ the stars in the sky every night.",
      options: ["design","seize","quote","observe"],
      correct_option: "observe"
  },
  {
      question: "Julie wants to buy a ______ computer so that she can carry it around when she travels.",
      options: ["memorable","portable","predictable","readable"],
      correct_option: "portable"
  },
  {
      question: "My grandmother likes to surprise people. She never calls ______ to inform us of her visits.",
      options: ["beforehand","anyhow","originally","consequently"],
      correct_option: "beforehand"
  },
  {
      question: "As the tallest building in the world, Taipei 101 has become a new ______ of Taipei City.",
      options: ["incident","geography","skylight","landmark"],
      correct_option: "landmark"
  },
  {
      question: "Many scholars and experts from all over the world will be invited to attend this yearly ______ on drug control.",
      options: ["reference","intention","conference","interaction"],
      correct_option: "conference"
  },
  {
      question: "John had failed to pay his phone bills for months, so his telephone was ______ last week.",
      options: ["interrupted","disconnected","excluded","discriminated"],
      correct_option: "disconnected"
  },
  {
      question: "The organic food products are made of natural ingredients, with no ______ flavors added.",
      options: ["accurate","regular","superficial","artificial"],
      correct_option: "artificial"
  },
  {
      question: "Jessica is a very religious girl; she believes that she is always ______ supported by her god.",
      options: ["spiritually","typically","historically","officially"],
      correct_option: "spiritually"
  },
  {
      question: "Jane usually buys things on ______. Her purchases seem to be driven by some sudden force or desire.",
      options: ["accident","compliment","justification","impulse"],
      correct_option: "impulse"
  },
  {
      question: "The week-long rainfall has ______ landslides and flooding in the mountain areas.",
      options: ["set about","brought about","come about","put about"],
      correct_option: "brought about"
  },
  {
      question: "In the cross-lake swimming race, a boat will be _____ in case of an emergency.",
      options: ["standing by","turning on","getting on","running down"],
      correct_option: "standing by"
  },
  {
      question: "The ground is slippery. Hold onto the rope and donâ€™t ______.",
      options: ["put off","turn up","let go","take apart"],
      correct_option: "let go"
  },
  {
      question: "______ the weather, the athletic meetings will be held on time.",
      options: ["Instead of","In relation to","On behalf of","Regardless of"],
      correct_option: "Regardless of"
  },
  {
      question: "If people keep polluting the rivers, no fish there will survive ______. ",
      options: ["at all cost","for a long while","in the long run","by no means"],
      correct_option: "in the long run"
  },
]
